

Miti Angira

RESEARCH ANALYST, SOULACE CONSULTING PVT. LTD.

Executive Summary

Intend to build a career in development sector with leading organizations, which will help me to explore myself fully and realize my potential in the service of society and planet.

Areas of Expertise

- MS Office
- Web Research
- MIS Reporting
- Report Writing
- Monitoring
- Documentation
- Data Analysis
- Coordination
- Lead Generation
- Infographics

Reach me at:

Contact No. - 08090757601 E-mail - miti12289@yahoo.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/miti-angira-

22a69237

Languages Known - English, Hindi

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



Research Analyst

SoulAce Consulting Pvt. Ltd., 2018-Present

- Conducting Primary and Secondary (Impact Assessment/ Baseline Study) research in CSR projects
- Writing reports, proposals and data analysis
- Documents designing (Proposals, Presentations and Reports etc.)
- Business Development

Additional Programme Officer (MGNREGA)

Govt. of Uttar Pradesh, 2013-2017

- Monitoring of the scheme from District Level
- Preparing various reports and handling scheme related grievances
- Coordination with block and state level team and support the implementation of the scheme according to the guidelines

EDUCATION



MBA (Finance & Banking)

Banasthali Vidyapith, Jaipur (2009-11)

B. Com

Bundelkhand University, Jhansi (2008)

Certificate Course in Corporate Social Responsibility

Indian Institute of Corporate Affairs, Gurugram, 2017-18

TRAINING / INTERNSHIP

Powergrid Corporation of India Ltd., Lucknow (U.P.)

Project Title: Corporate Social Responsibility of POWERGRID

Duration: Nov 27th 2017 to Dec 16th 2017

Description: During Internship gained a complete understanding of CSR policy of POWERGRID and its process of implementation of CSR Projects, Monitoring & Evolution and Impact Assessment. I also learned writing project proposals, MoU and documentation of projects.